ICICI LBR General Insurance has reported
a strong financial performance for
FY2025 with its profit after tax (PBT)
rising by 30.7% to ₹25.08 billion up
from ₹19.19 billion in
FY2024. The company's gross direct premium
income (GDI) grew 8.3% to
₹268.33 billion,
outpacing the industry growth of
6.2% adjusted for the new one-year
accounting norms. GDP growth stood at an
impressive
11%. The insurer also reported a 30% jump
in profit before tax (PBT) to ₹33.1
billion for the year. Q4 PBT saw a
slight dip of 4.2% to ₹6.68
billion. The combined ratio, a key measure of
underwriting performance, improved
slightly to
102.8% for FY2025 from
103.3% a year ago.  EARLIER.  Reflecting
operational
stability.  The board has proposed a
final dividend of ₹7 per share taking the
total dividend for FY2025 to ₹12 and
50 per share.  ICICI Lombard Solvency
Ratio stood at a robust
69X, comfortably above the regulatory minimum
of 1.5X while Return on Average Equity
improved to
19.1% With a focus on digital innovation, the
company continues to strengthen its position
in the market through AI-driven sessions and
customer-centric services